[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "How do you actually pronounce your name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Charlize Theron.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "What is the correct South African, dare I say it, African way of pronouncing this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Charlize Theron.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "And you quite consciously went and taught yourself how to speak in an American accent, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Do you speak African certainly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Can you speak African to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "So you speak it completely fluently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Oh, I think more fluently than I speak English.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Woody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Guilty as charged?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "None of this -- there's no truth to it whatsoever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "But he calls you Chuck?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chuck"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Heading that way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Because I want to actually work until I'm 108 and I don't think you can't have longevity if you just kind of fall back on one aspect of what you are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "There's never the safe one, is there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CD", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Well, I don't think human beings are -- I think we're pretty complicated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Oh, dear God, what is this, an hour show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Yes, we got plenty of time, seriously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Do you really love the aging process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "So far, I said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Is that because it's obviously treating you quite well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Look, I'm only 35.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "So you get to these random houses, and what do you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I -- the first thing I do is I inspect every closet and drawer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "There are guys going to say who is this weirdo?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "It's fascinating watching you because I know you don't like watching yourself, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "I've gotten a lot better.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Do you know how much money you've taken at the box office in movies you've been in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "God, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "That's not bad, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "That sounds good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "You don't care how much they make, these films?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "I care.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars"]}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Which one would you prefer at this stage of your career?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "HERON: I guess I would take the one that makes the billion dollars, but the critics don't care for it because then I can go make seven of the ones that I love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Hey, Todd, do we even have factory work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I'm sorry.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Todd"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "I mean, when you look back on it now, obviously brilliant for you in your career -- but to actually play that role, what was the experience like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "CC", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "That was the greatest gift I think I've ever been given in my career.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Academy Award"]}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Yes, look, it's absolutely amazing to win an Academy Award.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Did you watch the Oscars as a young girl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I did, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "ORGAN: Have you met him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Academy Award"]}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "When did you meet him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "The first time I met him, I had just won the Academy Award.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "And what did he say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "The nicest things that any icon or hero could possibly say to you, things that I'm so not deserving of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nelson Mandela"], "LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Just, you know, giving me credit for being a South African and kind of putting South Africa on the map, which I didn't, but I'll take that any day from Nelson Mandela.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Any other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africans"]}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Who else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I don't know if they were women but I know another category South Africans have won.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "How much of it is down to what happened, if anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Look, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "What is the main reason do you think that it is so bad in South Africa, and what can be done to tackle it properly do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "I think it is a lack of education.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "How do you get them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "You can go to our Web site, Charlizeafricaoutreach.org, and you can buy them there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ":", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "And directly help?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Yes, directly -- look, here is the thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "What is the single biggest problem that the young in South Africa just don't really want to use condoms or even know much about them, is that the problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "It is knowledge.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tatiana"]}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "What was it about the story here which grabbed your attention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Well, I loved Tatiana's book and, you know, this is a story that is particularly relevant to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "But where does this rank for you personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "It really ranks with me strongly because the subject matter is so personal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kristin Scott Thomas"]}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", ",", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "What was the thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I think Kristin Scott Thomas, you know, who I first worked with on \"The English Patient\" is, you know, one of the smartest, best actresses.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "And Harvey, when does the film get released here in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Movie opens next Friday.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harvey"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "I mean, did you ever meet Margaret Thatcher?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "I never did, but as a liberal.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret Thatcher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "And that I think is often the greatest characteristic of any leader, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "She put her principles first.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110716pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "How are your liberal friends going to react, Harvey, when you seem to be the one man who rehabilitates the Thatcher image for the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "I'm going to be run out of all my social circles, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harvey", "Thatcher"]}}]